Julie-Marie Charmillon

Rue des Aloes, Quartier Balestrino, Bâtiment A 20000 Ajaccio, Corse-du-Sud, France ⊠ ghjuliamaria.c@gmail.com

☎ 06 11 97 05 64

— Career Objective

Middle school teacher with four years' experience seeks a teaching position online to share my knowledge. I would love to utilize my energetic attitude and instructional abilities to help students who need private tutoring make progress in English.

Work experience

2018-2019 French Ministry of National Education, Arthur Giovoni Middle School (Ajaccio, France), Contract ESL Teacher.

French Ministry of National Education, Finosello Vocational School (Ajaccio, France), Contract ESL teacher.

2017-2018 French Ministry of National Education, Baleone Middle School (Ajaccio, France), Contract ESL teacher.

2015-2016 French Ministry of National Education, Georges Clémenceau Secondary School (Sartène, France), Contract ESL teacher.

French Ministry of National Education, Camille Borossi Middle School (Vico, France), Contract ESL teacher.

Education

2016-2017 **Preparatory class to the French PGCE**, distance learning with CNED concurrently with a language exchange at the Michigan State University (USA). Hickory Corners, Michigan, USA

2013-2014 Master's degree, Molecular Chemistry speciality.

Bordeaux 1 University, France

2012-2013 **Bachelor's degree**, Sciences and Technologies Chemistry speciality. Bordeaux 1 University, France

2010-2012 **Intensive foundation degree**, "Engineering Schools Training". Pasquale Paoli University, France

2010 **A-Levels equivalent**, Science stream, with honours.

J10 A-Levels equivalent, Science stream, with honours Laetitia Bonaparte Secondary School, France

Skill

- Prior teaching experience
- English language proficiency (TOEIC certificate with 845/990)
- Computer skills
- Writing/editing

- Communication
- Patience
- Adaptability
- Ability to give constructive feedback

Miscellaneous

- Driving Licence
- Boating Licence
- French First Aid Certificate
- Hobbies: swimming (winner of the national French Championship 2007), freediving, sailing, traveling

References

References available on request.